Hi!
I'm Kelli.
Now that we've evened out her complexion with a foundation, we're going to go back and cover up any little areas that may need a little bit more coverage.
That's why I like to conceal after I've done my foundation, because foundation will give you some coverage, but is not necessarily made to give you a ton of coverage on little blemishes or anything like that.
I like to conceal afterwards because I like to see what kind of coverage I can get out of foundation first.
It's kind of unnecessary to put on a ton of makeup if you don't need it, if your foundation will do the job for you.
Also, if you do you a little bit of concealer after your foundation, it's going to stay on a lot better for you.
What happens a lot of times is when you apply your concealer before your foundation, it will have kind of a tendency to be wiped off as you're applying your foundation.
Applying afterwards will give you a little bit better coverage and keep your foundation on a little bit longer for you.
We're just going to use our concealer brush and just kind of pat it on any areas of concern, any areas that we want a little bit more coverage on.
Of course, a little bit on the eye area.
I like to use a brush because it blends it a lot better than say a sponge or even your fingers.
That just gave us a little bit of extra help just covering up any little blemishes or anything like that under the eye area.
That's how you would want to use a concealer when you're trying to achieve a perfect canvas look.